

JAYDEEP DAS

B.Tech Student & Self UI/UX Designer and Developer

Energetic UI/UX Designer. Skilled in Flama, Adobe xd and Excellent Wireframe and Prototype Designing. Have completed several projects, including internship and have industrial level experience

"Design is not just what it look like and feel like. Design is how it works" -Steve Jobs (Founder of Apple)

🚁 jaydeep.das@outlook.in



+91-7432803902



West Bengal, India



WORK EXPERIENCE AND INTERNSHIP



Advanced

Trainee Engineer 3rd Feb, 2022 - Ongoing



Tata Consultancy Services

Working as an Intern (UI/UX Designer & Developer)

7th May, 2021 - 30th Jul, 2021



ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

B.Tech (Pursuing)

2018-2022

University - Maulana Abul Kalam Azad University of Technology (M.A.K.A.U.T)

1st Sem - 6.63 2nd Sem - 7.61 3rd Sem - 8.23 4th Sem - 10.00

5th Sem - 9.50 6th Sem - 9.91 7th Sem - 10.00

10th+2

2018

Board - Central Board of Secondary Education (C.B.S.E)

Obtain Percentage - 71%

10th

2016

Board - Central Board of Secondary Education (C.B.S.E)

Obtain CGPA - 8.0



SKILLS, TOOLS & FRAMEWORKS

UI/UX Design (Primary)

Figma, Framer, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, Balsamiq, Wireframe Designing, Interactive Prototype, Web/Mobile Design

Frontend Development (Primary)

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React, React-Native

Data Science

Data Analysis, Machine Learning, Deep Learning

Other Language

Python, C/C++



UI/UX DESIGN

Freelancer Web Deisgn | Zenatix Assignment

https://www.behance.net/gallery/127638639/Freelancer-App-Zenatix-UIUX-**Assignment**

https://www.behance.net/jaydeepdas2

https://dribbble.com/jaydeep_das2000

https://bit.ly/2Sfrk1Z

https://github.com/JaydeepDas2000

https://jovian.ai/jaydeep-msd





8









Playing PC games





Travelling





Lenskart - Spectacles Glasses App

Design

https://www.behance.net/gallery/127100563/Lenskart-Spectacles-Glasses-App

CoinX | Easy pay app

Design

https://www.behance.net/gallery/126537613/CoinX-Easy-Pay-App-Payment-Application

** For more UI/UX Design | Visit my behance account : https://www.behance.net/jaydeepdas2

PROJECTS

Autonomous Driving Car using CNN

Source Code: https://github.com/JaydeepDas2000/ SelfDrivingCar_FinalYearProject

Customer Review Sentiment Analyzer (This is for TCS Inframind Season-4 | 2nd Round)

Source Code:

https://github.com/JaydeepDas2000/PyAnalyzer_Restaurant_TCS_InfraMind Youtube: https://youtu.be/TuV4TRK1Aps

Analysis and Prediction for acceptance of Credit Card by Data Analysis and Machine Learning with Python (Naïve Bayes, KNN, Decision Tree, Logistic Regression are used)

Python Notebook:

https://jovian.ai/jaydeep-msd/predict-credit-card-acceptance

Classavio | Freedom of Education

I was working as frontend Developer Freelancer

Live Website : https://classavio.com/

Video Game Sales Analysis

Python Notebook: https://jovian.ai/jaydeep-msd/video-game-sales-analysis

** For more Development Work | Visit my Portfolio : https://bit.ly/2Sfrk1Z



- Learned Data Structure and Algorithms in Python from Jovian
- Learned Deep Learning with Pytorch: Zero to GANs from Jovian
- Learned Data Analysis with Python: Zero to Pandas from Jovian
- Learned Machine Learning with Python from Globsyn Finishing School
- Learned Data Analysis with Python from Globsyn Finishing School
- Learned The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing form Google Digital Unlocked
- Learned Become a Software Developer from Linkedin Learning
- Learned Master In-Demand Professional Soft Skill from Linkedin Learning

** All the certificate are provided on my portfolio : $\underline{\text{https://bit.ly/2Sfrk1Z}}$



I got Position of Vice School Captain in Kendriya Vidyalaya Berhampore

PERSONAL PROFILE

Father's Name : Malay DasDate of Birth : 21st July, 2000

Gender : MaleNationality : India

Jaydeep Das